{
  "decks": {
    "5678": {
      "name": "katakana",
      "author": "batman",
      "isPublished": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "ア",
          "back": "a"
        },
        {
          "front": "イ",
          "back": "i"
        },
        {
          "front": "ウ",
          "back": "u"
        },
        {
          "front": "エ",
          "back": "e"
        },
        {
          "front": "オ",
          "back": "o"
        },
        {
          "front": "カ",
          "back": "ka"
        },
        {
          "front": "キ",
          "back": "ki"
        },
        {
          "front": "ク",
          "back": "ku"
        },
        {
          "front": "ケ",
          "back": "ke"
        },
        {
          "front": "コ",
          "back": "ko"
        },
        {
          "front": "サ",
          "back": "sa"
        },
        {
          "front": "シ",
          "back": "shi"
        },
        {
          "front": "ス",
          "back": "su"
        },
        {
          "front": "セ",
          "back": "se"
        },
        {
          "front": "ソ",
          "back": "so"
        },
        {
          "front": "タ",
          "back": "ta"
        },
        {
          "front": "チ",
          "back": "chi"
        },
        {
          "front": "ツ",
          "back": "tsu"
        },
        {
          "front": "テ",
          "back": "te"
        },
        {
          "front": "ト",
          "back": "to"
        },
        {
          "front": "ナ",
          "back": "na"
        },
        {
          "front": "ニ",
          "back": "ni"
        },
        {
          "front": "ヌ",
          "back": "nu"
        },
        {
          "front": "ネ",
          "back": "ne"
        },
        {
          "front": "ノ",
          "back": "no"
        },
        {
          "front": "ハ",
          "back": "ha"
        },
        {
          "front": "ヒ",
          "back": "hi"
        },
        {
          "front": "フ",
          "back": "fu"
        },
        {
          "front": "ヘ",
          "back": "he"
        },
        {
          "front": "ホ",
          "back": "ho"
        },
        {
          "front": "マ",
          "back": "ma"
        },
        {
          "front": "ミ",
          "back": "mi"
        },
        {
          "front": "ム",
          "back": "mu"
        },
        {
          "front": "メ",
          "back": "me"
        },
        {
          "front": "モ",
          "back": "mo"
        },
        {
          "front": "ヤ",
          "back": "ya"
        },
        {
          "front": "ユ",
          "back": "yu"
        },
        {
          "front": "ヨ",
          "back": "yo"
        },
        {
          "front": "ラ",
          "back": "ra"
        },
        {
          "front": "リ",
          "back": "ri"
        },
        {
          "front": "ル",
          "back": "ru"
        },
        {
          "front": "レ",
          "back": "re"
        },
        {
          "front": "ロ",
          "back": "ro"
        },
        {
          "front": "ワ",
          "back": "wa"
        },
        {
          "front": "ヲ",
          "back": "wo"
        },
        {
          "front": "ン",
          "back": "n"
        }
      ]
    },
    "1576171671007": {
      "name": "Boy Pablo",
      "author": "batman",
      "isPublished": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "q",
          "back": "p"
        },
        {
          "front": "q",
          "back": "w"
        },
        {
          "front": "four",
          "back": "tomorrow"
        },
        {
          "front": "more",
          "back": "cards"
        },
        {
          "front": "another",
          "back": "one"
        },
        {
          "front": "five",
          "back": "more"
        }
      ]
    },
    "1576171677469": {
      "name": "Dad Jokes",
      "author": "batman",
      "isPublished": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "WHy chcken cross",
          "back": "he dumb"
        },
        {
          "front": "s",
          "back": "s"
        }
      ]
    },
    "1576192741859": {
      "name": "done",
      "author": "batman",
      "cards": []
    }
  }
}